openuserjs.org 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | About | OpenUserJS

Your privacy is critically important to us. At OpenUserJS.org _(OUJS)_ we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. _(We also can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)_
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law _(DMCA and TOS mutually inclusive and adhered to)_ , develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

### Website Visitors __

Like most website operators, OUJS may collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. OUJS’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how OUJS’s visitors use its website. From time to time, OUJS may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

OUJS also may collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol _(IP)_ addresses. OUJS does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information __

Certain visitors to OUJS’s website choose to interact in ways that require OUJS to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that OUJS gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide an OAuth/OpenID service. In each case, OUJS collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction. OUJS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics __

OUJS may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, OUJS may monitor the most popular scripts. OUJS may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, OUJS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information __

OUJS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that:

  * _(i)_ need to know that information in order to process it on OUJS’s behalf or to provide services available at OUJS’s website, and

  * _(ii)_ that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using OUJS’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. OUJS will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, OUJS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when OUJS believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of OUJS, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an OUJS website and have supplied your email address, OUJS may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with OUJS and our products. We primarily use our discussion announcements to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request _(for example via one of our feedback mechanisms)_ , we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. OUJS takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### JavaScript __

Some features contained within our site require JavaScript to be enabled. OUJS visitors who do not wish to have JavaScript enabled should set their browsers to disable JavaScript, with the drawback that certain features of OUJS’s website may not function properly without the aid of JavaScript.

### Cookies __

#### First Party __

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. OUJS uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of OUJS website, and their website access preferences. OUJS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using OUJS website, with the drawback that certain features of OUJS’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Third Party __

Some operations of this site may need third party cookies enabled. This is an ongoing discussion on development.

#### Local Shared Object __

OUJS does not currently utilize Flash based technology at this time thus no "Flash Cookies".

### Ads __

While we at OUJS don't currently have Ads if any ever are implemented Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by OUJS and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes __

Although most changes are likely to be minor, OUJS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in OUJS’s sole discretion. OUJS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. On occasion forum announcements may be made regarding changes in terms for the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
